One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
That's why I start a
journey with you, we can!
Traveling from sea to sea
that it's just a fantasy
There are tons of unimaginable truth
Don't turn a blind eye
Common sense is just the mind of the masses
I've never seen the end of
the world with my own eyes
That's why we've got to go,
Captain Live-By-My-Own-Rules
Who says it's impossible?
Nothing has started yet
I want to know everything now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can!
This moment
We can! I can!
This great feeling
Now, now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The Mink Tribe
Etetetetete...
"Ete"?
That's right! Raizo runs with that kind of rhythm.
I think he has this kind of power.
Ninpo - Blindfold Technique!
Guess who!
I-Is it Kanjuro?
I mean I know you're the only person there.
Look out! Duck!
Hey! Stop the silly ninpo nonsense...
Oh no! Those two fell!
Damn! What was that thing that fell on us out of the blue?!
I don't know. I think it was a bloody person with knives stuck all over his body...
What?!
Or just a small monkey.
You're scaring me!
What made you think that?!
Kin'emon! Kanjuro!
Did they fall into the water?
Let's go save them!
Luffy-dono! We're both okay!
That's Kin'emon!
Good! They're alive!
Go ahead! We'll catch up soon!
What is he talking about? No way!
Let's go back down!
Hey, Dragon! Head back down!
Ryunosuke, head back...
Hey, Ryunosuke...
How can we tell this poor guy to go back...
Seems like he wants to finish his job as soon as possible.
He's suffering.
Let's let him keep going.
So cute...
I'm sorry but we're gonna go ahead!
See you guys later!
Understood!
Hey! I won't allow you to enter the country!
Go ahead!
Huh? I think I just heard an unknown voice.
Come on, Ryunosuke!
You can do it!
Luffy!
Isn't that the top?!
What?
Oh! It is!
A little more to go, Ryunosuke!
The top?!
The top is close at hand!
Oh! So fast!
Ryunosuke! Make a final sprint!
Keep going! Ryunosuke!
Just a little more to go! Run!
You're almost there!
Yes! I'm starting to see something!
Ryunosuke! Come on! It's right there!
Ryunosuke!
You can do it, Ryunosuke!
We made it!
To the top!
We finally made it!
Ryunosuke! Good job!
We're here at Zou!
You're turning back to a drawing.
Hey, wait!
Ryunosuke!
This is absurd.
It's just a bad drawing.
Hey, hold it right there, you bastards!
Is that how you thank him for bringing you up here?!
We're in unknown territory.
We shouldn't look back.
You're right but...
Usopp! Ryunosuke was a good guy, wasn't he?!
Always pay attention to what lies ahead. Look.
That must be a gate into the country.
There is certainly civilization on the elephant's back.
There's a watchtower but no guards.
It's not security befitting a country.
Tsk! They're so cold!
Honestly! You guys snapped out of it too quickly!
Hey, Usopp! Come up here!
It's amazing!
You climbed the watchtower so quickly!
It's awesome!
So this is the back of the elephant!
No kidding!
Is this really the elephant's back?!
It's so interesting!
There's a massive, millennia-old elephant...
And there's a country on its back!
Yeah!
It has a forest, a river, and a town!
This sure is awesome!
It's exactly like an island!
Usopp! That tree's like a whale!
You're right!
The town is bigger than I thought!
But that town is sort of...
Luffy jumped down!
I knew he'd do that.
Do you see old "Eyebrows"?
No.
This place is too high to see anybody.
Zoro, shouldn't we wait for Kin'emon and Kanjuro?
It's not as vast as a continent.
Let's just go.
Wait, wait!
I'm coming with you guys!
He didn't have to jump. The gate's open.
No, I think this is...
Yeah, it's not actually open...
Someone destroyed it.
You're right.
This trail looks strange too.
It's too wide to call it an animal trail in a forest.
Hey, this is some pretty serious destruction!
And it's still fresh.
Are Sanji and the others gonna be okay?!
What a mess!
I couldn't see it from up there but what's going on here?!
Let's proceed with caution!
What?! We don't really know the residents here and we have other enemies?!
Whoa-whoa, hey!
W-W-W-Wait a minute, guys! Please!
You don't need to rush like that!
It's hard to walk.
Yeah, it's elephant's skin.
There are flowers in such strange spots.
What happened to Bariete?
The Lesser Minks passed through the gate.
He might've been taken down!
It's a town!
No one's here!
What's wrong with this country?!
They're all run-down!
Hey! Sanji! Nami!
Chopper! Brook! Momo!
Oh, and the gas guy.
Well, forget about him.
What happened here?
I smell the faint odor of gunpowder...
And gas, do you?
What's this all about? Can't we just lie back in a peaceful country sometimes?!
What?! What is it?!
Do you see something?!
I got this.
Did she just...
...jump in midair?!
What the...?!
Wait! Stop, Carrot!
Forget about them-teia!
More importantly, we have an invader in the Whale Forest!
Talking animals?!
They're the Mink Tribe!
Oh?! I-Isn't that outfit...
...Nami's?!
What is that weapon?
I felt a shock for a moment!
We have an invader in the Whale Forest?!
Yes, we're in trouble!
The Guardians will be mad!
An animal?!
A human?!
Hey, you!
Where did you get that outfit?!
What did you do to Nami?!
Are they a cannibal tribe?
Don't say such a scary thing!
I'm sorry! Don't eat me!
Look how high she can jump!
Do all of them have physical abilities like that?!
How is it?!
Do you see something, Carrot?!
I do! Maybe it's a little too late!
On the other side of Kurau City,
there's a disturbance in the Whale Forest!
I thought so! Let's go, Warney!
Get on, Carrot!
We don't have time to
transport you-teia guys!
Do as I say!
Go through the Rightrump Forest to your right
and turn left at a deep dark swamp...
You'll reach the Rightflank Forest!
You'll find the corpse of your-teia friend there!
C-Corpse?!
Wait at the Rightflank Forest!
We'll be there later!
Do you think they-teia are gonna be okay?
Those were the Straw Hats.
Huh? They-teia are gonna be shocked.
It's a shame but there's nothing we can do.
What's done is done.
The one who just invaded the Whale Forest is probably a pirate, Straw Hat Luffy.
He's their-teia captain but I'm sure the Guardians will show no mercy!
They were killed!
She said there's a corpse...
Which means they weren't cannibalized.
That's not the problem! Cut it out!
Calm down!
Old "Spiral Eyebrows" is with them.
He won't let anyone be killed.
Yeah. They're not gonna be killed that easily!
This must be a trick to make us upset and submissive!
You're right. I can't believe it.
Tra-guy-kun.
Your friends must be here, right? Is there any way to make contact?
No.
I didn't even expect to see them again.
But now I remember.
I forgot that I had a Vivre Card.
It belongs to our navigator, Bepo.
Oh yeah, you had a talking polar bear in your crew!
Is he a Mink too?!
Yeah.
This is where he was born.
But he didn't remember much about this island.
Because he left the island when he was little.
I've known him for a decade.
We can trust him.
If you wanna get reliable information, let's head straight.
Oh, I looked around from up there before!
If we go straight, there'll be a town!
We don't know who are there!
Are we gonna be okay?!
The cannibal tribe might be there...
It's better than going along with the unknown animal.
Let's follow him.
Whale Forest
Rubber...
Moo Golova!
Bell!
Why isn't Electro having any effect?!
That's it! Stop right there!
I know him!
Even if you know him, he's an invader!
I guess we gotta stop you by force!
Don't get in our way!
No! Jean Bart!
Damn! This is too much to handle!
He's too strong!
That's enough, Guardians!
A fluttering object!
A banana!
Yeah! I got a banana!
Whale Forest Guardian (Bull Mink)
Roddy
Whale Forest Guardian (Gorilla Mink)
BB
Yum! Yum, yum, yum...
So this is how you handle them.
A dog?
Battlebeast Tribe (Dog Mink)
Wanda
You-teia are Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?
I'm Wanda.
Battlebeast Tribe (Rabbit Mink)
Carrot
She's Carrot.
We won't do anything to you so stop resisting.
There are a bunch of strange creatures in this country.
It's like having a ton of Choppers.
What's with them?!
I didn't even do anything but they attacked me!
That's because you-teia invaded the forest where you mustn't enter.
Oh! Wh-What are you doing?!
Guardians!
We'll take him out of here!
Please forgive him!
For Wanda's sake...
Let's retreat, Roddy!
BB!
Pedro!
Everyone, retreat!
Was I surrounded?
Just be thankful this wasn't a moonlit night.
Hey, Straw Hat, don't you remember us?
We took care of you after the Paramount War!
I'm shocked!
Oh! You're the talking bear from Tra-guy's crew!
Tra-guy?
No, we work under Trafalgar Law!
Navigator of the Heart Pirates
Guardians's helper Bepo
The Heart Pirates!
That's what I said.
No, you didn't!
Well, we've been reading newspapers!
There was a whole bunch of surprising news!
We're allied, aren't we?
Is our captain here too?
Yeah, Tra-guy's here!
You got it wrong again! Who is that?!
Tra-guy is Law.
Oh yeah? I didn't know that.
So our captain, he's here! Yeah!
Captain, I can't wait to see you!
Center of the elephant's back
Kurau City
I guess there's no doubt that it was attacked.
This city could have as many as several hundred thousand residents but not a single person is here.
We shouldn't be out in the open like this!
The enemies must be around here still!
Is this a device for torture?
We can't even tell whether the enemies are humans or not.
There are so many claw marks.
Yeah, what are those?!
Hey, come see this.
It's a giant footstep.
Do you think it's an elephant?
Did some monsters and beasts attack the Minks' country?
But looking at those claw marks, it might be internal discord.
One thing is for sure.
This country was suddenly ruined only one or two weeks ago.
Th-Then Sanji and everyone else...
...were involved in it?!
Ruined?
That's why no one's there.
This centuries-old country's name is
Mokomo Dukedom.
When I trace my memories back to just a half-month ago, I can see everyone's happy face.
This country was ruined by...
...Jack!
Oh! What is this?!
What's going on?!
There'll be a Rain-Ruption!
Climb a tree!
Get on Warney!
I'll take you to the Rightflank!
Your friends are there!
Great! So Sanji and the others are there!
What's wrong?!